

const STORE = [
    {
      question: 'Who won the NBA Finals in 2009?',
      answers: [
        'Los Angeles Lakers',
        'Boston Celtics',
        'San Antonio Spurs',
        'Cleveland Cavaliers'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Los Angeles Lakers',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the record for total number of seasons played by a player?',
      answers: [
        '22',
        '21',
        '20',
        '19'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '21',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who scored 100 points in one game?',
      answers: [
        'Kobe Bryant',
        'Jason Kidd',
        'Larry Bird',
        'Wilt Chamberlain'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Wilt Chamberlain',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many players have been traded eight times in their career?',
      answers: [
        'One Player',
        'Two Players',
        '10 Players',
        '20 Players'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Two Players',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is on the NBA\'s official logo?',
      answers: [
        'Kenyon Martin',
        'Michael Jordan',
        'Magic Johnson',
        'Jerry West'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Jerry West',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which team did the Seattle Supersonics become?',
      answers: [
        'New York Knicks',
        'Oklahoma City Thunder',
        'Houston Rockets',
        'Los Angeles Clippers'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Oklahoma City Thunder',
    },
    {
      question: 'How many teams are on the Western Conference and Eastern Conference?',
      answers: [
      '15 each',
      '18 each',
      '20 each',
      '30 each'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '15 each',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which player was NOT drafted out of high school?',
      answers: [
        'Kobe Bryant',
        'Kevin Garnett',
        'Shaquille O\'neal',
        'LeBron James'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Shaquille O\'neal',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which state has the most NBA teams?',
      answers: [
      'New York',
      'Texas',
      'California',
      'Florida'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'California',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is the youngest NBA player to be drafted?',
      answers: [
        'Andrew Bynum',
        'Andre Drummond',
        'Blake Griffin',
        'Keyon Dooling'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Andrew Bynum',
    }
];